Mykyta Kuzmytskyi

PYTHON DEVELOPER



+38 067 799 92 13 (@mykytakuzmytskyi)



nykytakuzmytskyi@gmail.com



mykyta-kuzmytskyi



github.com/MykytaKuzmytskyi



Kyiv, Ukraine

SKILLS

- OOP, Design patterns
- TDD, SOLID, DRY principles
- Algorithms and data structures
- Pvthon 3.7+
- Django, Django ORM, Django REST
- FastAPI, SQLAlchemy
- PostgreSQL, SQLite, Redis
- HTML, CSS
- Requests, bs4, Selenium, Scrapy
- Docker
- Git/Github

EDUCATION

MASTER'S DEGREE IN TIMBER AND WOOD

Technical University in Zvolen

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- Python course at Mate academy
- SQL course at w3schools
- How to Think Like a Computer Scientist: Interactive Edition
- Python for network engineers

LANGUAGES

- English
- Ukrainian C2
- Slovak C1

PROFILE

Engineer by education with good communication skills in multiple languages, a team player with attention to detail, looking for an opportunity to be part of a professional development team. I have commercial Python scripting experience and have done several of my own projects in 1 year. I have experience with Python core, OOP, Django and Django REST frameworks using the SOLID concept, unit testing, Git version control system, I also have experience with SQL and relational databases.

EXPERIENCE

PYTHON DEVELOPER

Freelance (Self employed)

May. 2023 - Present

- Web Scraping: BeautifulSoup, Requests & Selenium
- Writing scripts
- Creation of custom projects

PYTHON DEVELOPER

Gravity electrical

Apr. 2022 - Feb. 2023

- Development of a CRM system for employees (writing models, templates and API views, serializers and forms, search systems, data validation, unit tests): Django, REST, Unit tests, Bootstrap4, Html/CSS, Docker, Celery.
- Web Scraping: BeautifulSoup, Requests & Selenium

PROJECTS

- Construction-company
- Cinema service API
- Library service API

AUTOCAD DESIGNER

Gravity electrical

Aug. 2021 - Mar. 2022

- Developed engineering drawings for power supply, smart home, security, and multimedia systems.
- Writing scripts to optimize work. (Python)